Guide to the Stanford University, Planning Office, Photographs PC0062
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Planning Office, photographs
circa 1905-2002
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Planning Office
PC0062
20.25 Linear Feet (39 boxes and 8325.12 megabytes)
Photographs produced by the Planning Office or by related offices prior to the inception of the Planning Office (such as Buildings and Grounds), as well as photographs from other sources that were acquired by the Planning Office.
Separated Materials
A portrait of Eldridge Spencer (first director of the Planning Office) taken by Ansel Adams was removed from accession 1990-052 and added to manuscript collection PHOTO 168, Ansel Adams Photographs.
Acquisition Information
Materials were transferred to the Stanford University Archives by the Planning Office in numerous accessions.
Access to Collection
This collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Scope and Contents note
This collection includes photographs produced by the Planning Office or by related offices prior to the inception of the Planning Office (such as Buildings and Grounds), as well as photographs from other sources that were acquired by the Planning Office. Of note are campus aerials, 1951-1970; a series of negatives with matching prints of academic buildings, largely from the late 1930s; a series of negatives with matching prints of the construction of Frost Amphitheater, 1936-37, Cubberley School of Education, and of the San Juan Hill reservoir, 1941; negatives from the construction of Hoover Tower; color images of the construction of the Science and Engineering Quad, 1997-98; and negatives of drawings, plans, and other documents for presentations at Board of Trustees Meetings, 1960s-70s. Other subjects include dormitories, cars on campus, Searsville dam, tree planting on campus, the Knoll (2004), and renovation of the Thomas Welton Stanford Art Gallery (2000). Those
Searsville Dam (Calif.); Photonegatives; Photoprints.; Stanford University. Science and Engineering Quad; Stanford University. Planning Office; Stanford University. San Juan Hill reservoir; Stanford University. Planning Office; Holub, Leo; Stanford University. Frost Amphitheater; Stanford University. Hoover Tower; Stanford University. Graduate School of Education
- Photographs, Series 1
  - Stanford University lands aerials, index to April 1951 flight, 1951 Apr 8 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stanford University lands aerials flown April 8, 1951, #1-28 to 1-59, 1951 Apr 8 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University lands aerials flown April 8, 1951, #1-61 to 1-104, 1951 Apr 10 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Stanford University lands aerials flown April 10, 1951, #4-4 to 4-32, 1951 Apr 10 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Stanford University lands aerials flown April 10, 1951, #4-33 to 4-65, 1951 Apr 10 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Stanford University lands aerials flown April 20, 1951, #5-23 to 5-54, 1951 Apr 20 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Stanford University lands aerials flown April 27, 1951, #6-41 to 6-55, 1951 Apr 27 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Stanford University lands aerials flown April 27, 1951, #7-3 to 7-17, 1951 Apr 27 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Stanford University lands aerials flown April 30, 1951, #8-32 to 8-43, 1951 Apr 30 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Campus aerials flown May 16, 1957, #1 to 28, 1957 May 16 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Campus aerials flown May 16, 1957, #30 to 78, 1957 May 16 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Campus aerials flown May 16, 1957, #80 to 128, 1957 May 16 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Campus aerials flown May 16, 1957, #130 to 174, 1957 May 16 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Campus aerials flown July 20, 1963, #1-1 to 1-7, 1963 Jul 20 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Campus aerials flown July 20, 1963, #2-1 to 2-8, 1963 Jul 20 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Campus aerials flown July 20, 1963, #3-1 to 3-8, 1963 Jul 20 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Campus aerials flown July 20, 1963, #4-1 to 4-7, 1963 Jul 20 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Campus aerials flown July 20, 1963, #5-1 to 5-8, 1963 Jul 20 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Campus aerials flown July 14, 1969, #1-1 to 2-9, 1969 Jul 14 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Campus aerials flown July 14, 1969, #3-1 to 4-9, 1969 Jul 14 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Campus aerials flown July 14, 1969, #5-1 to 5-10, 1969 Jul 14 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Campus aerials flown July 14, 1969 - record of borrowed and missing prints, 1969 Jul 14 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University lands aerials, n.d. (post Tresidder, prior to Green West) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Academic campus, assorted oblique aerials (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Campus, oblique aerials from distance, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Crothers Hall, obliques (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Dormitories, oblique aerials (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Hospital and shopping center, aerial, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Law School site aerials flown, November 23, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Shopping center site, oblique aerials, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Shopping center and medical sites aerial, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Shopping center, oblique aerials, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - SLAC aerial flown, February 26, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - SLAC oblique aerial (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Stanford industrial park site, oblique aerials 1956 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Wilbur dormitories site, oblique aerial 1954 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Unidentified building aerials (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Quad II - Alumni building, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Quad II - Music building, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Quad II - Music building, color transparencies, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Quad II - Music building, captions for photos and misc. items (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Quad II - Music building model, 1955 (with negatives) (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Quad II - Music building model, color prints 1956 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Quad II - Post Office, p.o. boxes, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Quad II - Student activities center model, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Quad IV - Applied Electronics Lab, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Quad IV - Chemistry buildings, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Quad IV - Electronics Research Lab, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Quad IV - General office buildings [now Cypress, Spruce, etc] (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Quad IV - Medical school site, obliques, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Quad IV - Medical school site, undated aerial, with negative (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Quad IV - Medical school aerial survey, 10-31-55 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Quad IV - Microwave lab, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Quad IV - Physics lecture hall, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Quad IV - Science quad model 1949, with negatives (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Quad V - Lagunita dormitory, oblique aerial (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Quad VI - Crothers Hall (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Quad VI - Stern Hall, interior, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Quad VI - Wilbur Hall, completion photos, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Quad VIII - War Memorial plaques, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Quad X - Married student housing (aerial of construction) (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Campus, miscellaneous views (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Construction, electrical lines (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Construction, Frost Amphitheater, 1937 (with negatives) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Construction, Wilbur Hall and Crothers, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Historical, campus lands (Coutts?) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Historical, 1906 earthquake damage on campus (with negatives) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Historical, Palo Alto, ca. 1900 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Land use - slides of existing and proposed land use maps, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Landscape photographs (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Non-Stanford photographs (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Other Universities - Zeta Psi house, Berkeley (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Planning exhibit, Trustees meeting, April 1958 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - SLAC - site photographs, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Buildings Show, 1948 (includes brochure) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Toyon Hall, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Negatives - campus photographs, ca. 1950 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Negatives - inner quad oblique (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Negatives - Men's Gymnasium and Library, ca. 1905 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Negatives - original construction on Quad (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Negatives - unidentified aerial (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Oversize aerials of campus (infrared and regular), circa 1970 (Box 5)
  - Negatives and matching prints of various views of the Quad
    - Administration building, negative (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Administration building, print (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Administration building, ca. 1941, negative (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Administration building, ca. 1941, print (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Administration building, front, negative (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Administration building, front, print (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Administration building, front, negative (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Administration building, front, print (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Jordan Hall, ca. 1941, negative (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Jordan Hall, ca. 1941, print (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Jordan Hall with parked cars, ca. 1941, negative (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Jordan Hall with parked cars, ca. 1941, print (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Quad, Art Gallery, Library (post 1919), negative (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Quad, Art Gallery, Library (post 1919), print (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Quad building, repair, negative (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Quad building, repair, print (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Quad from oval (Jordan Hall side), negative (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Quad from oval (Jordan Hall side), print (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Quad from oval (Jordan Hall side), negative (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Quad from oval (Jordan Hall side), print (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Quad from oval (Jordan Hall side), negative (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Quad from oval (Jordan Hall side), print (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Quad from oval (History Bldg side), negative (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Quad from oval (History Bldg side), print (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Quad, front view with parked cars, ca. 1941, negative (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Quad, front view with parked cars, ca. 1941, print (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Quad, front view with parked cars, ca. 1941, negative (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Quad, front view with parked cars, ca. 1941, print (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Quad, front view, (left) ca. 1941, negative (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Quad, front view, (left) ca. 1941, print (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Quad, front view, (right), ca. 1941, negative (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Quad, front view, (right), ca. 1941, print (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Quad, Hoover Tower, ca. 1941, negative (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Quad, Hoover Tower, ca. 1941, print (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Quad, Hoover Tower, ca. 1941, negative (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Quad, Hoover Tower, ca. 1941, print (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Quad, Hoover Tower, ca. 1941, negative (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Quad, Hoover Tower, ca. 1941, print (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Quad, Jordan Hall to Hoover Tower, ca. 1941, negative (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Quad, Jordan Hall to Hoover Tower, ca. 1941, print (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Quad, Jordan Hall to Hoover Tower, ca. 1941, negative (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Quad, Jordan Hall to Hoover Tower, ca. 1941, print (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Negatives and matching prints of other campus buildings
    - Chemistry building, negative (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Chemistry building, print (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Chemistry building, negative (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Chemistry building, print (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Chemistry building, corner with tree, negative (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Chemistry building, corner with tree, print (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Chemistry building and labs, negative (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Chemistry building and labs, print (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Chemistry and Museum from oval, negative (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Chemistry and Museum from oval, print (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Chemistry building with truck, negative (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Chemistry building with truck, print (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Chemistry building with S.U. truck, negative (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Chemistry building with S.U. truck, print (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Cubberley School of Education construction, negative (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Cubberley School of Education construction, print (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Cubberley School of Education construction, negative (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Cubberley School of Education construction, print (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Cubberley School of Education construction, negative (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Cubberley School of Education construction, print (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Cubberley School of Education construction, negative (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Cubberley School of Education construction, print (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Encina service pipes, 1945, negative (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Encina service pipes, 1945, print (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Encina service pipes, 1945, negative (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Encina service pipes, 1945, print (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Engineering labs (?), rear view, 1936, negative (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Engineering labs (?), rear view, 1936, print (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Library (1919) and Art Gallery, negative (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Library (1919) and Art Gallery, print (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Memorial Auditorium, installing trees, negative (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Memorial Auditorium, installing trees, print (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Memorial Auditorium, installing trees, negative (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Memorial Auditorium, installing trees, print (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Memorial Auditorium, installing trees, negative (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Memorial Auditorium, installing trees, print (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Negatives and matching prints of other subjects
    - Cars, parked, 1939, negative (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Cars, parked, 1939, print (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Cars parked at top of oval, circa 1941, negative (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Cars parked at top of oval, circa 1941, print (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Cars parked at top of oval, 1939, negative (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Cars parked at top of oval, 1939, print (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Cars parked on oval, circa 1941, negative (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Cars parked on oval, circa 1941, print (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Cars parked in front of Quad, circa 1941, negative (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Cars parked in front of Quad, circa 1941, print (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, 1936, negative (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, 1936, print (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, 1936, negative (damaged) (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, 1936, print (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, 1936, negative (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, 1936, print (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, 1936, negative (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, 1936, print (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, 1936, negative (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, 1936, print (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, 1936, negative (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, 1936, print (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, 1936, negative (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, 1936, print (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, 1936, negative (damaged) (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, 1936, print (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, tree planting, 1937, negative (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, tree planting, 1937, print (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, negative (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, print (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, negative (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, print (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, negative (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, print (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, negative (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, print (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, tree planting, negative (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, tree planting, print (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, negative (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, print (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, negative (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, print (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, tree planting, negative (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, tree planting, print (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, tree planting, negative (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, tree planting, print (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, tree planting, negative (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, tree planting, print (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, tree planting, negative (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, tree planting, print (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, negative (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Frost Amphitheater construction, print (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Galvez Street, repair by Encina Hall, 1941, negative (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Galvez Street, repair by Encina Hall, 1941, print (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Lagunita Lake, trimming new rip rap, January 1943, negative (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Lagunita Lake, trimming new rip rap, January 1943, print (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Lagunita Lake, trimming new rip rap, January 1943, negative (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Lagunita Lake, trimming new rip rap, January 1943, print (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Lagunita Lake, trimming new rip rap, January 1943, negative (dorm in background) (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Lagunita Lake, trimming new rip rap, January 1943, print (dorm in background) (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Lagunita Lake, trimming new rip rap, January 1943, negative (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Lagunita Lake, trimming new rip rap, January 1943, print (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Lagunita Lake, trimming new rip rap, January 1943, negative (boathouse in background) (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Lagunita Lake, trimming new rip rap, January 1943, print (boathouse in background) (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Road intersection, 1939, negative (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Road intersection, 1939, print (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir, construction, 1941, negative (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir, construction, 1941, print (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir, construction, 1941, negative (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir, construction, 1941, print (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir, construction, 1941, negative (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir, construction, 1941, print (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir, construction, 1941, negative (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir, construction, 1941, print (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir, construction, 1941, negative (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir, construction, 1941, print (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir, construction, 1941, negative (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir, construction, 1941, print (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir, construction, 1941, negative (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir, construction, 1941, print (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir, construction, 1941, negative (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir, construction, 1941, print (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir, construction, 1941, negative (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir, construction, 1941, print (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir (?), construction, 1941, negative (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - San Juan Hill reservoir (?), construction, 1941, print (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Searsville Dam, negative (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Searsville Dam, print (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Searsville Dam, negative (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Searsville Dam, print (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Sheep on grass in front of Quad, negative (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Sheep on grass in front of Quad, print (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Tree planting, negative (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Tree planting, print (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Tree planting, negative (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Tree planting, print (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Tree planting, negative (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Tree planting, print (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Trolley by Encina, negative (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Trolley by Encina, print (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Truck in front of old service station on Santa Teresa, negative (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Truck in front of old service station on Santa Teresa, print (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Truck on Santa Teresa, negative (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Truck on Santa Teresa, print (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Truck on Santa Teresa, negative (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Truck on Santa Teresa, print (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Truck close up, rear, on Santa Teresa, negative (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Truck close up, rear, on Santa Teresa, print (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Truck with driver, negative (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Truck with driver, print (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Truck close up, front, negative (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Truck close up, front, print (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - Unidentified man, negative (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - Unidentified man, print (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Negatives without prints
    - Earth moving machine, negative (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Encina Hall, side steps with car and truck, negative (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Encina Hall, side view, negative (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Encina Hall, side view, negative (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Encina Hall, side view, negative (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Encina Hall, side view, negative (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Encina Hall, with two cars and cyclist, negative (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Hoover Tower construction, negative (Box 8, Folder 34)